("Hanging By a Moment")
♪ Desperate for changing ♪
♪ Starving for truth ♪
♪ I'm closer to where I started ♪
♪ I'm chasing after you ♪
♪ I'm falling even more in love with you ♪
♪ Letting go of all I've held on to ♪
♪ I'm standing here
until you make me move ♪
♪ I'm hanging by a moment here with you ♪
♪ Forgetting all I'm lacking ♪
♪ Completely incomplete ♪
♪ I'll take your invitation ♪
♪ You take all of me now ♪
♪ I'm falling even more in love with you ♪
♪ Letting go of all I've held on to ♪
♪ I'm standing here
until you make me move ♪
♪ I'm hanging by a moment here with you ♪
♪ I'm living for the only thing I know ♪
♪ I'm running and not
quite sure where to go ♪
♪ And I don't know what I'm diving into ♪
♪ Just hanging by a moment here with you ♪
♪ There's nothing else to lose ♪
♪ There's nothing else to find ♪
♪ There's nothing in the world ♪
♪ That can change my mind ♪
♪ There is nothing else ♪
♪ Desperate for changing ♪
♪ Starving for truth ♪
♪ I'm closer to where I started ♪
♪ I'm chasing after you ♪
♪ I'm falling even more in love with you ♪
♪ Letting go of all I've held on to ♪
♪ I'm standing here
until you make me move ♪
♪ I'm hanging by a moment here with you ♪
♪ I'm living for the only thing I know ♪
♪ I'm running and not
quite sure where to go ♪
♪ And I don't know what I'm diving into ♪
♪ Just hanging by a moment here with you ♪
♪ Just hanging by a moment ♪
♪ Hanging by a moment ♪
♪ Hanging by a moment here with you ♪